{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/5243","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5243","name":"Vergotes Poultry & Fish Inc.","address":"16523 Harper","zipcode":"48224","owner":"","licenseNumber":"013904","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-82.94226,42.41298","geojson":{"id":"5243","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.942262418,42.412975757]},"properties":{"name":"Vergotes Poultry & Fish Inc.","owner":"","address":"16523 Harper","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"013904","establishmentid":"5243","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4936","name":"Checker's #3426","address":"16511 Harper Rd","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1315","name":"Taco Bell #1930","address":"16511 Harper","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"4082","name":"Smokey's Bar-B-Q","address":"16555 Harper Ave.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"480","name":"Yahoo Lounge","address":"16656 Harper","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2265","name":"Louie's Ham & Corn Beef","address":"16661 Harper","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1585","name":"Maya Angelou Elementary School","address":"5959 Whittier","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2162","name":"White Castle #59","address":"16701 Harper Ave. ","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"3738","name":"Popeye's #941","address":"16701 Harper Ave.","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"5290","name":"Charlie's Jolly Cones","address":"9194 Whittier","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"689","name":"I-Rock Nightclub","address":"16350-54 Harper","zipcode":"48224"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43719","inspectionDate":"2018-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36669","inspectionDate":"2016-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"Food","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the bottom Shelf","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s) knives","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On top of the Ice machine","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"No Test strips","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"No Paper toweling","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Behind the WALK-IN COOLER","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2010-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2010-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to prevent grease accumulation/dripping/draining."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"To prevent contamination of food or food related items","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On top of the Ice machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5243"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}